I am the kettle. Do you know who "Kettle Kun" is?
I'm going to start the kettle now.
Let's go!
Kettle and Idol
Personally, I've always wanted to try bungee jumping.
You don't have a bungee?
No, I don't.
I'm very adventurous.
Are you a serious car guy?
Yes, I am. That's something I'll never outgrow.
I'm taking it with me on the road.
Is she in her second year?
Yes, that's right. She is going to be in a transitional year with me.
This is really what the members say to me.
They say, "That's enough, that's enough.
There are some amazing people.
Many of them are unconscious.
Rinna, you're singing that song again," they often say.
Idols and Idols
Well, here I am again today, the halfway kettle from StarLast!
Let's call today's guest idol!
Here he is!
Hello everyone!
I'm Norina from Crown Pop.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Rina, thank you for coming.
Thank you very much.
It's the spring of your graduation.
That's right.
You majored in film at the University of Hokkaido's College of Technology.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
You're in your first year at a place where you have seniors.
I'm sure you're doing a lot of specialized work.
Are you going to make a graduation project?
Do you make videos?
I was the performer.
I see.
I was offered a role in a scenario written by the director.
It was my graduation project.
The director also made a film for your graduation project?
Yes, I did.
If the director decided to kill the film.
I wouldn't be able to graduate.
I'm taking you with me.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I said, "This is that," and I lost it.
I did my graduation project.
He'll be exiled.
I'm going to be exiled along with him.
What do you mean by that?
All you do is make movies.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to hear about it.
I'd like to hear from the director.
A director, a sound guy...
What about you?
We were divided into different fields.
You're making a commercial film.
That's right.
Just like a team.
We're all in this together.
Yes, we are.
In the name of graduation.
How long is the film?
It's limited to 15 minutes.
That's the school's rule.
There are regulations.
You have to make a 15-minute film.
That's right.
And the professor and I...
He critiqued it.
That's right.
Some of them won awards.
Awards?
And other things?
Yes, sir.
Within the school?
Within the school, there are a lot of people involved.
They chose it as an award.
That's right.
The award was announced on graduation day.
Uh-huh.
That's right.
I got one, too, on a stroke of luck.
What did you get for your car in the war?
I was able to balance schoolwork and my idol career.
I was able to balance schoolwork and being an idol.
You know?
I got an award for being awesome.
It was at school.
So there are people in the seminar who are going to be in the show?
Someone who's ahead of you there?
Yes.
So you're all in it now? - Yes.
Yes, we're waiting for an offer.
Waiting for offers?
Sometimes... this way.
Heh.
That's right.
It's so interesting that I keep asking.
By the way, what kind of role are you playing this time?
About four this time.
Four?
That's right.
What? You're a vertical holder?
I've been in four films.
I've played idols.
Well, I know how to play idols.
I also played office workers and high school students.
Office worker.
High school student.
I also played high school students.
I played a pretty wide range of roles.
I see.
So you've worked on a variety of productions?
That's right.
Heh.
And the filming?
Yes, sir.
There's a certain time of year.
Summer and fall.
That's when you start editing.
Yes, that would be...
Interesting.
Yes, it would be.
I'd like to have an exhibition.
What do you mean?
I'm not that good at it.
This program...
Mr. Nisshi.
Mr. Pieru
Mr. Sadaaki
Eimaru
Frog-chan
Thank you to all of you!
Thank you very much!
Please look forward to the next installment!